export const questionArray = [
  {
    question: "What is the name of Protagonist in One Piece?",
    options: ["Monkey D. Luffy", "Roronoa Zoro", "Uzumaki Naruto", "Asta"],
    answer: "Monkey D. Luffy",
    hint:
      "Lorem ipsum HINT NO.1 dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit est sociosqu risus, ut consequat accumsan dictumst libero fames pellentesque commodo non.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the magic-less boy in Black Clover?",
    options: ["Satoru Gojo", "Usopp", "Yami Sukehiro", "Asta"],
    answer: "Asta",
    hint:
      "Lorem ipsum HINT NO.2 dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit est sociosqu risus, ut consequat accumsan dictumst libero fames pellentesque commodo non.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the Captain of The Golden Dawn?",
    options: [
      "Yami Sukehiro",
      "William Vangeance",
      "Black Maria",
      "Levi Ackerman",
    ],
    answer: "William Vangeance",
    hint:
      "Lorem ipsum HINT NO.3 dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit est sociosqu risus, ut consequat accumsan dictumst libero fames pellentesque commodo non.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the King of the Pirates?",
    options: [
      "Julius Novachrono",
      "Gol D. Roger",
      "Monkey D. Luffy",
      "Saitama",
    ],
    answer: "Gol D. Roger",
    hint:
      "Lorem ipsum HINT NO.4 dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit est sociosqu risus, ut consequat accumsan dictumst libero fames pellentesque commodo non.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who has the title of World's Strongest Swordsman in One Piece Universe?",
    options: [
      "Dracule Mihawk",
      "Akagami no Shanks",
      "Silvers Rayleigh",
      "Roronoa Zoro",
    ],
    answer: "Dracule Mihawk",
    hint:
      "Lorem ipsum HINT NO.5 dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit est sociosqu risus, ut consequat accumsan dictumst libero fames pellentesque commodo non.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the Luffy's first crewmate?",
    options: ["Nico Robin", "Roronoa Zoro", "Usopp", "Nami"],
    answer: "Roronoa Zoro",
    hint:
      "Lorem ipsum HINT NO.6 dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit est sociosqu risus, ut consequat accumsan dictumst libero fames pellentesque commodo non.",
  },
  {
    question: "Monkey D. Luffy's first bounty?",
    options: [
      "30,000,000 Berries",
      "100,000,000 Berries",
      "300,000,000 Berries",
      "500,000,000 Berries",
    ],
    answer: "30,000,000 Berries",
    hint:
      "Lorem ipsum HINT NO.7 dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit est sociosqu risus, ut consequat accumsan dictumst libero fames pellentesque commodo non.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Kira in Death Note?",
    options: ["Light Yagami", "Ichigami Senku", "L", "Watari"],
    answer: "William Vangeance",
    hint:
      "Lorem ipsum HINT NO.8 dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit est sociosqu risus, ut consequat accumsan dictumst libero fames pellentesque commodo non.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who gave the Death Note to Light Yagami?",
    options: ["Ryuk", "L", "Misa Amane", "Watari"],
    answer: "Ryuk",
    hint:
      "Lorem ipsum HINT NO.9 dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit est sociosqu risus, ut consequat accumsan dictumst libero fames pellentesque commodo non.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the S-Class Hero no.14 in One Punch Man?",
    options: ["Saitama", "Metal Bat", "Watchdog Man", "Genos"],
    answer: "Genos",
    hint:
      "Lorem ipsum HINT NO.10 dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit est sociosqu risus, ut consequat accumsan dictumst libero fames pellentesque commodo non.",
  },
];
